aajtv.com 2007-10-10

# AAJ TV : Pakistan's Premier Channel : Privacy Statements

**PRIVACY POLICY**   
We do not share any data or information about you (collected for whatever reason and by whatever means or provided by you to us for whatever reason and by whatever means) with any third party. Ever, except when required to provide it under orders from a competent Court of Law. 

There is a limited amount of information any web site can gather about its visitors without directly asking the visitors any questions. Examples of this information include: the browser you are using, the time that you spend on our web site, etc. This information is collected to keep our web site optimized to the preferences of the majority of our visitors with a view to serving them better. 

Then, there is information that a visitor provides when he joins mailing lists, participates in polls, promotions and contests, or fills out surveys. Our privacy policy covers all such information. We keep this information strictly to ourselves and use it only to serve you better. This information is not and will not ever be shared with any outside party. 

Our privacy policy does not and cannot be applied to information that you choose to put up in sections that are open to public, that is, classified advertisements, message boards, discussion forums, etc. Naturally our privacy policy does not and cannot cover this information. It is simply impossible for us to check others using this information for their own valid or invalid purposes. 

We do not also give, lease or sell email addresses of visitors to outside parties. However, we do occasionally send to our visitor's news and announcements about us, our sister web sites and the services we or our sister web sites offer. So, if you provide us your email address, for whatever reason, please expect to receive such emails from us
